Something I want to speak on is the value of extending love, not for the sake of the
person having to respond, but for the understanding that when you send it, it is received regardless.
Now, what I mean about that is in the specific instance of when you know someone has had
a loss or someone has gone through something traumatic or just any time that you know that
somebody may be in a situation where they could use some love. I think a lot of times we tell
ourselves they want privacy or they need space or, you know, they don't want to be bothered.
And then we will actually not reach out. I remember when I miscarried and I had told a friend
and they just never, they like said one thing to me and then I never heard from them again.
And I addressed it later and they said, Oh, well, I just thought you needed space. I said,
but I didn't ask for space. And they were like, Oh, well, I just thought that's what you needed.
But I think what it really happens is that a lot of us, you know, we are afraid of our emotions and
we are not in touch with the way that compassion when it's needed makes us feel. And then sometimes
we're all so busy, but we have to be conscious enough to know that the act of reaching out
is where the actual energy comes from and is received. Even if the person doesn't respond,
they are receiving that energy that you sent in other ways.